Finish a painting with me!
We're painting with oil — let's put some final touches together.
For red, I chose Rembrandt Permanent Red Deep, artist-quality oil paint.
Next goes Van Gogh Cadmium Yellow — a gorgeous non-transparent colour. I just love it.
As an addition, I'm using Winsor and Newton Fluorescent Yellow.
Look how bright it is — sick.
Next we have Rembrandt Turquoise — just a tiny bit as an addition.
Rembrandt Periwinkle. It's transparent, and I'm absolutely obsessed with it.
Looks almost like Pantone Veri Peri. Viridian hue as an addition to create the shadings.
I like to organise my work — paints in separate boxes so I know where to search for what I need.
I use scent-free turpentine as a medium.
And that's how the final touches come together.
Mad Mojo — art with a little madness in it.